Guide to the Women's National Book Association Records
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Materials Received in 1986
  - Foul. Ms., Etc., 1985 (Box 69)
  - Foul. Ms., Etc., 1985 (Box 69)
  - Foul. Ms., Etc., 1986 (Box 69)
  - Book Review Info and Correspondence, undated (Box 69)
  - Type Specifications, undated (Box 69)
  - Production Forms, 1984-1986 (Box 69)
  - Los Angeles Chapter, undated (Box 70)
    - Board Meeting, undated (Box 70)
    - Board Meeting Flyers, undated (Box 70)
    - Board Members, undated (Box 70)
    - Board Minutes & Agenda (2 Folders), undated (Box 70)
    - Board Roster, undated (Box 70)
    - Calendar, undated (Box 70)
    - Chapter, undated (Box 70)
    - Chapter--By-laws, undated (Box 70)
    - Chapter--Data Sheets, undated (Box 70)
    - Chapter--Newsletters (2 Folders), undated (Box 70)
    - Program flyer, undated (Box 70)
    - Program Information sheets (2 Folders), undated (Box 71)
    - Publicity (4 Folders), undated (Box 71)
    - Reports, undated (Box 71)
    - Treasurer Report, undated (Box 71)
  - Nashville Chapter, undated (Box 71)
  - Southern Chapter Broadcasters Association, undated (Box 71)
  - Southern California Chapter, undated (Box 71)
  - Washington/Baltimore Chapter, undated (Box 71)
- Series VI: Subject Files, National Chapter, 1963-1991
  - Correspondence (Box 72)
    - Betty Brandis, 1974-1979 (Box 72)
    - Sylvia Cross, 1984-1986 (Box 72)
    - Suzanne Lavoie, 1986-1988 (Box 72)
  - Awards (Box 73)
    - Claire Friedland, 27 October 1988 (Box 73)
    - Effie Lee Morris, 1984 (Box 73)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1986 (Box 73)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1987 (Box 73)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1988 (Box 73)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1986 (Box 74)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1987 (Box 74)
    - Lucile M. Pennell, 1988 (Box 74)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1989, (2 Folders) (Box 75)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, Washington D.C., 1989 (Box 75)
    - Lucile M. Pannell, 1990, (3 Folders) (Box 76)
    - Ann H. Eastman, 1986 (Box 76)
    - WNBA Award, 1986 (Box 76)
    - Bookwomen Award, 1984 (Box 76)
    - Bookwomen Award, 1987 (Box 76)
    - Skinner Award, 1978-1980 (Box 76)
    - Certificate for Bookwomen, 1987 (Box 76)
    - Citation from American Library Association, 1986 (Box 76)
  - Committees: Goals and Objectives, Questionnaire Sent to Chapter (Box 77)
    - Binghamton, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Boston, undated (Box 77)
    - Detroit, undated (Box 77)
    - Los Angeles, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Nashville, 1985 (Box 77)
    - New York, 1985 (Box 77)
    - San Francisco, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Washington, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Annual Report of the President, 1989 (Box 77)
    - Annual Report of the President, 1990 (Box 77)
    - Annual Report of the President, 1991 (Box 77)
    - Computer Printout of Raw Data, undated (Box 77)
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 77)
    - Final Questionnaire, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Long Range Planning, June 1989 (Box 77)
    - Presidential Report, 1983-1984 (Box 77)
    - Questionnaire Drafts, January-April 1985 (Box 77)
    - Questionnaire Results, 1985 (Box 77)
    - Report of Board of Directors, 27 June 1986 (Box 77)
    - Rough Draft Table, undated (Box 77)
    - Table, undated (Box 77)
  - Committee: 70th Anniversary, 1987 (Box 78)
    - Archival Material, undated (Box 78)
    - Budget, undated (Box 78)
    - Campaign for Nominees, undated (Box 78)
    - Ceremony, undated (Box 78)
    - Committee Meetings, undated (Box 78)
    - Correspondence, 1986-1987 (Box 78)
    - Finance Committee, undated (Box 78)
    - Finance Fund Raising, undated (Box 78)
    - Follow-up Final Report, undated (Box 78)
    - Gala, undated (Box 78)
    - Invitations, undated (Box 78)
    - Judge, undated (Box 78)
    - Liaison Committee, undated (Box 78)
    - List Maintenance, undated (Box 78)
    - Meetings--Minutes, undated (Box 78)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 78)
    - New York Public Library, undated (Box 78)
    - Non-Winner (2 Folders), undated (Box 79)
    - Program Inserts, undated (Box 79)
    - Program Inserts and Invitations, undated (Box 79)
    - Publicity, undated (Box 79)
    - Publicity, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Report of the Board, June 1988 (Box 79)
    - Souvenir Program, 1987 (Box 79)
    - Souvenir Program Compilation (including 3 copies of souvenir booklet), undated (Box 79)
    - VIP Letters and Replies, undated (Box 80)
    - Winners, undated (Box 80)
    - Winner’s Official Bibliographies, undated (Box 80)
    - Winners--Sources, undated (Box 80)
  - By-Laws, 1983 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings Report, 1986-1988 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings, 1978-1982 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings, 1968 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings, 1987 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings--Los Angeles, 1988 (Box 81)
  - Board Meetings, 1989 (Box 82)
  - Board Meetings-- Washington, D.C., 1989 (Box 82)
  - Board Meetings, 1990 (Box 82)
  - Financial Records (Box 83)
    - Binghamton Chapter, 1982-1987 (Box 83)
    - Boston Chapter, 1982-1986 (Box 83)
    - Cancelled Check for WNBA, undated (Box 83)
    - Career Patterns Survey, undated (Box 83)
    - Chapter Information, 1977-1984 (Box 83)
    - Cleveland Chapter, 1982-1985 (Box 83)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1986 (Box 83)
    - Detroit Chapter, 1980-1984 (Box 83)
    - Finance Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 83)
    - Income, 1982-1986 (Box 83)
    - Internal Revenue--Tax Exemption, 1977 (Box 83A)
    - Internal Revenue--Tax Exemption, 1982 (Box 83A)
    - Legal--Incorporated Data, New Jersey, 1967-1984 (Box 83A)
    - Los Angeles Chapter, 1981-1984 (Box 83A)
    - Memorial Fund, 1980 (Box 83A)
    - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 83A)
    - Miscellaneous Expenses, 1985-1986 (Box 83A)
    - Nashville Chapter, 1979-1986 (Box 84)
    - New York Chapter, 1981-1986 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Award--Bank Statement, 1982-1986 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Expenses, 1984-1985 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Expenses, 1988-1986 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Finances, 1983 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Finances, 1984 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Finances, 1985 (Box 84)
    - Pannell Finances, 1986 (Box 85)
    - Pannell-Engeldinger Correspondence, 1981 (Box 85)
    - Pannell Saving Account, undated (Box 85)
    - Procedures--National, 1980-1983 (Box 85)
    - San Francisco Chapter, 1979-1982 (Box 85)
    - Constance Lindsay Skinner Award, 1979-1987 (Box 85)
    - Sustaining Members, 1979-1986 (Box 85)
    - Treasurer-Annual Reports, 1976-1986 (Box 85)
    - Washington/Baltimore Chapter, 1980-1986 (Box 85)
  - American Book Council, undated (Box 86)
  - Archives--Miscellaneous Publicity, undated (Box 86)
  - Brochure, undated (Box 86)
  - Historical, New York City Survey, undated (Box 86)
  - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 86)
  - National President’s Reports, undated (Box 86)
  - National Secretary’s (2 Folders), undated (Box 86)
  - Procedure Manual, undated (Box 86)
  - Publisher’s Weekly, undated (Box 86)
  - Savvy Project, undated (Box 86)
  - MLA-WNBA/WISP, 1985 (Box 87)
  - MLA-WNBA/WISP, 1986 (Box 87)
  - WISP, 1980 (Box 87)
  - Audio tape cassettes, 1979-1986 (Box 87)
  - WNBA Literary Contract, 6 March 1979) (Box 88)
  - WNBA Award, 1982-1984 (Box 88)
  - Scott Berg/Maxwell Perkins, 17 February 1981 (Box 88)
  - WNBA Los Angeles Chapter--Authors, March 1980 (Box 88)
  - Question and Answer Moderated By S. Cross, undated (Box 88)
  - National WNBA Board Meeting in NYC, 1986 (Box 88)
  - Americana, 1954 (Box 89)
  - Bookwomen, 1936-1988 (Box 89)
  - Bookwomen--70 Who have made a difference, undated (Box 89)
  - Bookwomen--Photographs, 1987 (Box 89)
  - Miscellaneous, 1958-1985 (Box 89)
  - Constance L. Skinner, undated (Box 89)
  - Women in the World of Words, 1967 (Box 89)
  - Binghamton Chapter (Box 90)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, 1963-1982 (Box 90)
    - Book and Author Dinner, 1967 (Box 90)
    - By-Laws, 1963 (Box 90)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1986 (Box 90)
    - Minutes of WNBA Meeting Minutes, 1963-1986 (Box 90)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963-1982 (Box 90)
    - Printed Materials, undated (Box 90)
    - Report for National Board Meeting, undated (Box 90)
    - Roster, 1963-1982 (Box 90)
  - Boston Chapter-- Report for National Board Meeting, undated (Box 90)
  - Cleveland Chapter-- Report for National Board Meeting, undated (Box 90)
  - Detroit Chapter
    - Board Meeting, undated (Box 90)
    - Board Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 90)
  - Los Angeles Chaper (Box 91)
    - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 91)
    - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 91)
    - Writers Conference, 1988 (Box 91)
  - Nashville Chapter--Miscellaneous, undated (Box 91)
  - New York Chapter
    - By-laws (Box 91)
    - Reports, 1983-1984 (Box 91)
  - Pittsburgh and Grand Rapids Chapter--Report, 1979 (Box 91)
  - San Francisco Chapter--Report, 1985-1986 (Box 91)
  - Washington/Baltimore Chapter--Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 91)
  - Washington/Baltimore Chapter--Report, undated (Box 92)
  - Washington Chapter
    - Archive, undated (Box 92)
    - Signature, undated (Box 92)
- Series VII: Materials Received 1992-2011
  - Detroit Chapter, 1991-1993 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Chapter, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - National Board Meeting, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Bookwoman, 1994-1996 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Charitable Contributions, undated (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - National chapter, undated (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Programs, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - JRS, 1994-1995 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - June Panel--Gay & Lesbian, 1995 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Miscellaneous Treasury, undated (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Rosters, 1993-1995 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Directory, undated (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - DYK, undated (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Membership, undated (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Annual Reports--Board Members, 1993-1995 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Stationary, undated (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Development, undated (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Publicity, 1994 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - National Chapter, undated (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - San Francisco Chapter, undated (Box 101, Folder 1 to 2)
  - National Chapter, 1996-1998 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Lucile M. Pannell Awards, 1995-1998 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Nashville Chapter
    - Photographs, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Agendas, Treasurers, Minutes, Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Newsletters, 1995-1996 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - News clippings, undated (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Athena Award, 1996 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Lucile M. Pannell Awards--Photographs, 1963-1998 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Bookwoman, 1997-1998 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Bookwoman, 1995-1996, 2011 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Bookwoman, 1994-1995 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors--Annual Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - National Chapter--Annual Reports, 1996-1998 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Internal Reports and Correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1997-1998 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Floppy discs, 1995-1996 (Box 102, Folder 10)
  - Detroit Chapter, 1992-1994 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - WNBA Award, 1994 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Nashville Chapter, 1993-1994 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Nashville Chapter, 1993-1994 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Corresponding Membership Chair, 1991-1992 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Corresponding Membership Files, 1988-1991 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Board Meeting Minutes, Chapter and committee reports, 1993 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Binghamton Chapter, 1990-1993 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - New York City Chapter (Box 104)
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Program--Author Reading, 1990 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Program--Trends in Global Marketplace, 1992 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Program Flyers, 1978-1990 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Treasurer’s Report, 1969-1987 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports and National Chapter, 1989-1991 (Box 104, Folder 6 to 8)
  - Chapter Newsletters--San Francisco, Los Angeles, Nashville, 1990-1991 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - National Chapter--Membership Letters, Recruitment, 1991 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - National Chapter-- Publicity and Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1976-1989 (Box 104, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Chapter, 1991-1992 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Detroit Chapter
    - By-Laws, 1978 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - 1965-1970 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - 1970-1974 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - 1976-1977 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - 1978-1979 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors--Minutes of Annual Meeting, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - WNBA Award, 1992 (Box 105, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors--Minutes of Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 13)
  - Supporting Documents for Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 105, Folder 14)
  - Bookwoman, 1956-1983 (Box 105, Folder 15)
  - Nominating Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 105, Folder 16)
  - Nashville Chapter, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 17)
  - New York City Chapter (Box 106)
    - Annual Directories, 1983-1993 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Annual Business Meeting Announcements and Elections, 1981-1990 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1990 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Annual Business Meeting, 1991 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports to National, 1978-1984 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - By-Laws, 1976-1989 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Board Meeting Minutes & Agendas, 1980-1984 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Board Meeting Minutes & Agendas, 1984-1987 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Board Meeting Minutes & Agendas, 1986-1988 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Board Meeting Minutes & Agendas, 1990-1991 (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Board Meeting Minutes & Agendas, 1987-1991 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Board Rosters, 1979-1991 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Did You Know?, 1979-1992 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Job Descriptions, 1986-1991 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Membership Surveys, 1980-1990 (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Membership Statistics, 1980-1981 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Membership Survey, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Membership, 1991 (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Membership Renewal, 1994 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Boston Chapter (Box 108)
    - 1992-1993 (Box 108, Folder 1 to 2)
    - Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 108, Folder 4 to 5)
    - Brochures and Membership Rosters, 1990-1996 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Newsletters, 1989-1997 (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - 1994-1995 (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - Nashville Chapter, 1996-1997 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - National Chapter, 1987-1988 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - WNBA Affiliate in Japan, 1968-1969 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Chicago Chapter, 1963-1972 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Amy Loveman Award, 1964-1970 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Little Rock Chapter, 1967-1970 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Lucile M. Pannell Award, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Grand Rapids Chapter, 1968-1969 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - United Nations, International Book Year, 1965-1972 (Box 109, Folder 8)
  - National Chapter, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - National Chapter, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 10)
  - Binghamton Chapter, 1964-1971 (Box 109, Folder 11)
  - Nashville Chapter, 2009-2010 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Nashville Chapter, 2010-2011 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Detroit Chapter, 1966-2009
    - Board Meeting Agendas, 1993-2009 (Box 112)
    - Board Meeting Minutes, 1994-2009 (Box 112)
    - Chapter Meeting Agendas, 2005-2008 (Box 112)
    - Chapter Meeting Minutes, 1987-2009 (Box 112)
    - Announcements, 2007-2009 (Box 112)
    - Bylaws and Policies (Box 112)
    - Membership Promotion and Brochures (Box 112)
    - Membership Surveys, 2005-2006 (Box 112)
    - Membership Rosters (Box 112)
    - Annual Reports, 1966-2009 (Box 112)
    - Annual Financial Reports, 1966-2003 (Box 112)
    - Special Projects, 2005-2008 (Box 112)
    - Programs, 2005-2009 (Box 112)
    - Donations, 2001-2002 (Box 112)
    - Bookwoman of the Year (Box 112)
    - Bank Statements, 2001-2002 (Box 112)
  - National Chapter
    - Board Rosters (Box 114)
    - Membership Directories (Box 114)
    - Minutes of and Reports to National Board Meeting, 1987-2005 (Box 114)
    - Parnell Award, 1999-2002 (Box 114)
    - 75th Anniversary (Box 114)
    - WNBA Award (Box 114)
    - Eastman Grant Material, 2002-2009 (Box 114)
    - Treasurer's Files
      - Financial Records, 1991-1998 (Box 113)
      - Financial Reports, 1998-2007 (Box 111)
      - Bylaws (Box 111)
      - Communication Plan (Box 111)
      - Directory (Box 111)
      - 80th Anniversary (Box 111)
      - Election, 2000, 2002 (Box 111)
      - Minutes-- Annual National Board Meeting, 2005-2008 (Box 111)
      - Claire Friedland (Box 111)
      - Financial Records, 1991-1999 (Box 115)
      - Chapter Financial Records and Correspondence, 1996-1999 (Box 115)
      - Financial Records, 2000-2006 (Box 116)